《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
你要我把那群调查局探员全都炸上天吗
You want me to blow up a couple of dozen FBI agents?
有什么问题吗
You got a problem with that?
沃克探员  我是杰克
Agent Walker, this is Jack.
让你的人撤出那栋楼  那是个陷阱
Get your men out of the building... It's a trap.
毒气罐还在吧
You got the canister?
很明显  霍奇斯是幕后主谋
Clearly, Hodges is behind this.
把他带去调查局审问
I want him taken to the FBI for interrogation.
妈  他是反社会者
He's a sociopath, mom.
他不会交代的  他一定会
He's not going to talk... he's going to want
以合作为条件来跟你谈交易
To make some kind of deal in exchange for his cooperation.
-妈  你不会出此下策吧  -奥利维亚
- Mom, you're not considering that. - Olivia...
你了解这个人  明白他都对罗格做了什么
You know what this man is, what he did to Roger.
是我搅了局  对吧
I've upset the cart, have I?
你为我们研制的生化武器
That bioweapon that you developed
不应用作私人用途
For us was not intended for personal use.
我想我们可以达成一致
I think we can both agree
你的家人没有必要
That there's no reason for your family
为你的错误付出代价
To pay for your mistakes.
这会让你心跳停止
This will induce a cardiac arrest
而且可以在你体内不留痕迹
And leave no trace in your system.
我们改变路线去西阿林顿医院
We are rerouting to west arlington hospital.
有阿尔梅达的消息吗
Have you heard from Almeida?
见到霍奇斯之前我给他打了电话
I called him before I met with Hodges.
他拿到毒气罐了吗
Has he secured the canister?
-很快  -他是你的人
- Soon. - He's your guy.
最好别搞砸了
He better not screw this up.
我相信他能把事办妥
I have faith he'll come through.
你为什么不回到局里让他们给你治疗下
Why don't you go back to FBI medical and let them treat you?
无药可救的
There is no treatment.
好不了了
There is no cure.
杰克  他们好像知道我们的计划
Almost like they knew, Jack.
他们在楼内布置炸药
They would have needed Time
总要花时间的
To wire this building with explosives.
这是我们计划搜索的最后一个区域
This is the last sector we were due to search.
杰克  怎么了
Jack, what is it?
你到底扮演什么角色
What is your involvement?
你头脑不清醒了
You're not thinking straight.
毒素在影响你的判断能力
The toxings starting to affect your judgment.
-快把枪放下吧  -你别动
- Now, why don't you put the gun down. - Don't you move!
我从没想过要伤害你  杰克
I never wanted to hurt you, Jack.
我告诉过你别管闲事
I told you to stay out of it.
这里需要帮助
We get some help here?
他开始抽搐了
This man's having a seizure.
以下情节发生在凌晨3点至4点间
The following takes place between 3 a.m. and 4 a.m.
鲍尔先生  你现在应该会感觉好很多
Mr. Bauer, you should be feeling better already.
我正给你静脉注射5毫升的盘多帕敏
I'm giving you five CC's of intravenous Pendopamine.
会缓解肌肉痉挛
It'll de-constrict your muscles.
坚持一下
Just hang in there.
别说话  你的声带还在痉挛中
Don't talk. Your vocal cords are in spasm.
究竟发生了什么事
What the hell happened?
托尼·阿尔梅达发现他全身抽搐
Tony Almeida found him in full seizure.
你给他的药包呢
What about the medication pack you gave him?
他没带
Wasn't carrying it.
制  制  制止
S-s-stop.
鲍尔先生  请不要讲话
Mr. Bauer,please don't speak.
制止
Stop...
托尼
Tony...
Tony?
我不明白
I don't understand.
他就是暗中协助的第二人
He's second man.
-杰克  什么  -快发全面缉捕通告
- Jack, what... - Put out an APB.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
快做
Do it!
所有巡逻队和周边小组注意
Attention, all patrols and perimeter teams,
我是A1小队
This is Alpha one.
现对托尼·阿尔梅达发出优先全面缉捕通告
I'm issuing a priority APB on Tony Almeida.
请小心行事
Approach with extreme caution.
托尼是盖尔维兹的同谋
He's colluding with Galvez
应做敌人对待
And should be considered hostile.
发现疑犯的小组  应万分小心
All units who engage the suspect should do so with extreme caution.
你真的需要给自己多点时间恢复
You really need to give yourself more Time to recover.
这里还有一个药包
Here's another med pack.
这次可别再丢了
Make sure he doesn't lose it.
我要去照顾其他伤者了
I need to go tend to the other wounded.
好吧  告诉我到底怎么回事
All right,tell me what the hell is going on.
托尼一直就是盖尔维兹一伙的
Tony was working with Galvez all along.
他利用了我们所有人来得到那个毒气罐
He used us, all of us, so that he could get to the canister.
等等  你是说
So, wait, what are you saying, that...
托尼杀了拉里
Tony killed Larry?
是的
Yeah.
他们肯定是在直升机降落时偷袭了他
They must have ambushed him as the chopper was setting down.
托尼藏在幕后以便掌控我们的搜索情况
Tony stayed behind so he could monitor our search,
设下圈套  确保盖尔维兹可以逃出搜索线
Set the trap and make sure Galvez could get beyond the perimeter.
天哪
Oh, god.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
这是我的错
This is my fault.
我还向你和总统担保他没问题
I vouched for him to you, to the president.
我犯了很严重很严重的错误
I made a terrible, terrible mistake.
我是觉得不大对劲
I felt that something was wrong.
事情凑到一起讲不通
Things weren't adding up.
我只是
I just...
我只是想要相信他
I just wanted to believe him.
A1小队  我是基尔纳探员
Alpha one, this is agent Kilner.
我是A1小队  请讲
Alpha one... go ahead.
沃克探员  我在D检查站
Agent Walker, I'm at checkpoint Delta.
这里有两个探员死亡  近距离直射
I've got two agents dead, shot point-blank.
车辆丢失
Their vehicle is missing.
他应该过了封锁线了
Okay, he's made it past the perimeter.
车辆跟踪装置已失灵  无法确认位置
Tracking on the vehicle has been disabled. Position is unknown.
扩大封锁线  继续寻找阿尔梅达
Widen the perimeter, and keep looking for Almeida.
如果找不到他  就找不到毒气罐
If we lose him, we lose the canister.
你找不到他的  他逃脱了
You're not gonna find him... he's gone.
我们得打电话给总统
We need to phone the president.
走吧
Let's go.
你逃出来了
You made it.
你好像很惊讶
You sound surprised.
鲍尔叫住你后  我可不确定你还能脱身
After Bauer called you out, I wasn't sure you would.
你不必担心杰克·鲍尔
You don't have to worry about Jack Bauer.
他不再是问题
He's not gonna be a problem.
毒气罐在哪里
So, where is the canister?
钱呢
Where's the money?
我们不是说好的嘛
Hey, that was our agreement.
一手交钱  再一手交货
Money first.
在这
There you go.
钱都在那里  汇到你账户上了
It's all there, wired into your account.
不相信可以查查
You can check it if you want.
我是要查查
I want.
没问题吧
Everything okay?
没问题
Yeah.
那毒气罐在哪里
So, where is the canister?
就在这里
Right here.
你要拿它来干嘛
So, what are you planning on doing with it?
不关你的事  对吧
Not really your business, is it?
要卖掉吗
You gonna sell it?
别做傻事
You don't want to do this.
买家到底是谁
Hey, who's the damn buyer?
毒气罐在哪里
Where's the canister?
他妈的毒气罐在哪里
Where is the damn canister?!
押送霍奇斯的一名海军陆战队员
One of the marines that was guarding Hodges
发现他正试图吞下某种东西
Noticed he was trying to swallow something.
他阻止了他  在毒药被完全吸收前
He intervened, got him to the hospital
把他送到了医院
Before the poison could be completely ingested.
这么说  他活下来了
So, he'll survive?
是的  阁下  医生很惊讶他能活过来
Yes, ma'am, but the doctors are surprised he pulled through.
那是因为他们从来没遇到过这种混蛋
That's because they never met the son of a bitch.
霍奇斯是怎样拿到毒药的
How did Hodges get this poison?
我们怀疑是一个宣称是他律师的女人给他的
We suspect from a woman who claimed to be his attorney.
宣称
Claimed to be?
她是个冒牌货
She was an impostor.
首府警察在五分钟前发现了
DC police found the body of Hodges' real attorney
真正的霍奇斯律师的尸体
About five minutes ago.
我们还在努力调查
We're still trying to determine
她是怎样成功通过安检的
How she managed to breach security.
总统阁下  是沃克探员和杰克·鲍尔
Madam President, agent Walker and Jack Bauer.
-接过来  -是  阁下
- Put them through. - Yes,ma'am.
我是泰勒总统
This is president Taylor.
蒂姆·伍兹也在这里
I'm here with Tim woods.
总统阁下
Madam President...
找到毒气罐了吗
Have you secured the canister?
阁下  恐怕没有
I'm afraid not, ma'am.
我们的疑犯逃出了封锁线
Our suspect escaped beyond the perimeter.
你们不是说封锁那区域了吗
I was told that the area was locked down.
怎么回事
What happened?
他有帮凶  总统阁下
He had help, Madam President.
是托尼·阿尔梅达
From Tony Almeida.
阿尔梅达
Almeida?
是的  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
他为我们做事的啊
He was working for us.
这只是表象
It only appeared that way.
他显然是在执行自己的计划
Apparently, he was pursuing his own agenda,
想要弄到毒气罐
Trying to get his hands on the canister.
总统阁下  我知道是我担保的他
Madam President, I know I vouched for him.
现在我能讲的只有
All I can tell you right now
我错了  很抱歉
Is that I was wrong and I'm sorry.
既然现在毒气罐在他手上
Now that we know he has the canister,
知道他打算用来做什么吗
Do we have any idea what he intends to do with it?
-还不知道  -那他在哪里
- No, not yet. - Or where he is?
我们已召集所有人员重新部署寻找线索
We're all hands on deck here, sir, regrouping to develop leads.
我可能有一条线索
I may have one.
在霍奇斯被拘捕时
As Hodges was taken into custody,
他叫嚣说  在他被捕后
He yelled at me about some larger group
还有更大的组织会继续行动
That would continue on after his arrest.
干出一些我无法阻止的事情
Something that I wouldn't be able to stop.
您觉得他指的是什么
What do you think he meant?
我确定的是
Well, all I know for sure
有人不想让霍奇斯开口
Is that someone doesn't want Hodges to talk.
霍奇斯被捕后不久
Shortly after he was arrested,
就有个女人假扮他的律师来见他
Hodges was visited by a woman impersonating his lawyer.
显然  她给了他某种致命毒药
She apparently gave him some kind of lethal drug,
因为十分钟后
Because ten minutes later,
霍奇斯便企图自杀
He tried to commit suicide.
企图自杀
Tried to commit suicide?
他还活着
Oh, he's still alive.
乔纳斯·霍奇斯是个十足的老顽固
Jonas Hodges was completely unrepentant.
肯定是有人强迫他自杀
Now, this suicide attempt must have been coerced.
很明显  他们揪住了他的软肋来威胁他
Well, obviously, they're holding something over him,
很有可能是他的家人
Most likely his family.
如果真是这样  总统阁下
If that's the case, Madam President,
我们得跟他谈谈
We need to talk to him.
杰克  即使今天发生了这一切
Jack, even after everything that's happened today,
我还是不允许极端的审讯方式
I will not allow any kind of coercive interrogation.
总统阁下  没这个必要  他会开口的
Madam President, that won't be necessary. He'll talk.
你怎么那么肯定
How can you be sure?
因为我们会给霍奇斯他需要的东西
Because we can offer Hodges something that he needs.
是什么
And what's that?
制造他死的假象
Proof of death.
这样就能让那些想干掉他的人相信
We can convince the people that wanted him dead
他真的死了
that they succeeded.
只有这样  霍奇斯才能保护他家人
It's the only way Hodges can protect his family.
总统阁下  目前
Madam President, right now,
他是我们唯一的线索
He's the only lead we've got.
我就当你这样做很必要了
I'll assume that was necessary.
别惹我
Don't start with me.
我可没这个心情
I'm not in the mood.
好吧
All right.
盖尔维兹先生决定把毒气罐藏起来不给我
Mr. Galvez decided to hide the canister from me,
所以我得想办法找到罐子
So, uh, I had to find out where it was.
我们得去送货了
We've got a delivery to make.
可以走了吗
Shall we go?
我觉得我们不该去
No, I don't think we should.
他们在等我们
They're expecting us.
我的看法是
Yeah, well, the way I see it,
他们会拿走我流血得来的这个毒气罐
They're gonna take this canister that I sweated blood for
然后丢在角落六个月不闻不问
And sit on it for six months.
他们会用它制造更多的病原体
They're gonna use it to make more pathogen.
我们以前有27个毒气罐  现在只有1个
We had 27 canisters; now we have one.
没错  我说一个足够了
Yeah, and I say one's enough.
听着
Look...
政府不稳定
The government's reeling.
联邦调查局软弱无力
The FBI is stretched thin...
混乱不堪  错误百出
Scrambling, making mistakes.
我们只需今天再发动一次袭击
Another attack today is all we need
就能让整个事态发展到崩溃的边缘
To push this thing right over the edge.
现在绝不是撤退的时候
This is no Time to pull back.
我建议我们今天就拿着毒气罐
I say we take that canister,
去完成任务
And finish the job off today.
我不是不同意
I don't disagree with you
但这由不得我们决定
But it's not our decision to make.
好吧
Fine.
就让你们那群乌合之众去执行吧
Then run it by your group or your gang or whatever the hell they are.
但是他们早晚会知道
But they'll know one thing.
不趁机斩草除根
You finish your enemy off when he's down.
他们就会死而复生的
You don't let him get back up and reload.
我敢打包票
I guarantee you,this thing's gonna be
再拖6个月后
A hell of a lot harder
局势会更加艰难
To pull off six months from now.
不管你怎么评价乔纳斯·霍奇斯
And you can say what you want about Jonas Hodges,
但事实是
The fact is,
他今天给我们提供了一个机会
He gave us an opportunity today.
我们抓着它吧
Let's take it.
我联系一下组织里
I'll contact the group.
好
Good.
她具体说什么了
What did she say exactly?
只说她有急事
Only that she needs to see you
要见你
And that it's urgent.
我听到了关于调查局这次搜捕的一些流言
I heard rumors about the FBI operation.
你妈妈会详细的告诉你的
I'm sure your mother will fill you in
奥利维亚
Olivia.
调查局的封锁被突破了是真的吗
Is it true the FBI perimeter was breached?
是的
I'm afraid so.
毒气罐已被带到了警戒线之外
The canister is now outside the cordon.
有什么办法能把它找回来吗
What are we doing to get it back?
蒂姆  你先回避一下好吗
Tim,would you excuse us for a moment?
当然
Of course.
怎么了
What is it?
打电话给司法部长
I need you to call the attorney general
起草一份给乔纳斯·霍奇斯的证人保护协议
And draft a witness protection agreement for Jonas Hodges.
证人保护
Witness protection?
您是认真的吗
You can't be serious.
不到一个小时之前
Less than an hour ago,
霍奇斯企图自杀
Hodges tried to kill himself.
我们认为他肯定是被胁迫的
And we all believe that he must've been coerced.
谁胁迫他
By whom?
还记得他之前的那次叫嚣吧
You remember his rant...
说他只是更大阴谋的冰山一角
That he is a cog in a larger conspiracy,
还有其他许多同伙前仆后继
That there are others who will carry on.
您认为是他们抢走了毒气罐
You think they're the ones who took the canister?
这个还需要调查
Well,we need to find out.
所以需要霍奇斯开口
Which is why we need to get Hodges to talk.
奥利维亚  我们觉得让那些想灭口的人
Olivia,we feel confident that he will
以为霍奇斯真的死了
If we can assure him that these people will believe
他就会说出线索
That his suicide attempt actually succeeded.
我们要让他人间蒸发
We need to make him disappear.
所以需要那个证人保护协议
Which is why I need the protection agreement.
没有别的让他开口的法子了
There is no other way he'll talk.
把他视为敌对分子
Designate him an enemy combatant,
对待他要像秋风扫落叶一般
Then treat him like one.
我们不能这么做
We don't do that.
至少我管理的政府不能
Not in this administration.
并不是说要给他自由了
And it's not as if he's getting a free pass.
他下半辈子都要在联邦监管之下过活了
He'll be under federal supervision for the rest of his life.
哦  是啊
Oh,yeah,
在科罗拉多洲100英亩的牧场里逍遥
On a hundred acre ranch in colorado!
你的亲生儿子死在他手里
This man murdered your son!
我的弟弟
My brother.
更不要提  数以百计的无辜平民
Not to mention hundreds of innocent civilians.
不用你提醒  我知道他做了什么
I don't need you to tell me what he's done.
很明显你需要我的提醒
Apparently you do.
-奥利维亚  别说了 -爸爸会怎么想
- Olivia,stop it! - What would dad say?
-你肯定问都不敢问  -你别说了
- I bet you're afraid to ask. - I said stop!
你觉得我就好受吗
Do you think this is easy for me?
难道他会觉得我不会伤心欲绝吗
if he think it doesn't tear me apart?
我是罗格的母亲
I'm Roger's mother.
但我同时也是美国的总统
But I am also the President of the United States
我手按圣经发过誓  要捍卫美国宪法
And I placed my hand on a Bible and swore to protect and defend the constitution.
你是我的参谋长
You are my chief of staff.
只管做好你的本职工作去
I need you to act like one.
乔纳斯·霍奇斯已关在调查局
Now,Jonas Hodges is at the FBI,
杰克·鲍尔马上就赶到
and Jack Bauer will be there shortly.
快点起草那个协议
I need an agreement drafted.
请照做
Do that please.
计划很简明
The plan is straightforward...
用托尼·阿尔梅达从斯塔克伍德
An attack today this morning
弄来的生化武器
During rush hour using the bioweapon
在今早高峰时段发动袭击
That Tony Almeida retrieved from Starkwood.
你们登陆上这个电话连线时
You should have each received a data pack
每人都会收到一份数据包
When you logged on to this call.
请看一下
Please open it now.
这次行动会被归咎于这个人
The attack will be attributed to this man,
吉布安·阿尔扎利安
Jibraan al-zarian.
他的尸体会留在现场
Whose body will be left at the scene.
留下的证据为
The evidence trail implicating him
捏造的电邮
Will include fabricated e-mails,
通话记录
Phone records,
和通过我们特选的
And a large wire transfer to his account
也门银行的帐户汇款
Via our favorite yemenI bank.
我在看这些材料
I'm looking at the briefing materials
看不出这人和恐怖组织
And I'm not seeing how this man is actually connected
有任何联系
To any terrorist group.
确实没有
He isn't.
按照之前讨论过的
As previously discussed,
用一个平民做掩护
There are considerable tactical advantages
会更有蒙蔽性
To using an innocent.
他的不可确定因素有多大
But what about his unpredictability?
他无所事事
Al-zarian has no agenda of his own.
比起恐怖分子
He'll in fact be easier to control and manipulate
更好控制和操纵他
Than a real terrorist.
估算伤亡人数有多少
So what are The casualty esTimates?
第三页有关于伤亡人数
Page three describes the casualties esTimates
和次级影响的估算
As well as secondary effects.
我们列出了
As you can see,we've listed
等会  先不要去管
Hold on Forget about
伤亡人数了
What casualties may or may not be.
我们在说几个小时之内
We're talking about launching a new operation
展开一次甚至连计划都没的新行动
In the next few hours. Without any planning.
而且只有一个毒气罐
And with only one canister.
行动计划已经有了
The plan for this operation was already in place.
只需抓紧时间
We'd just be accelerating the Timetable.
我们本来要花半年去准备
We were going to have six months to prepare.
不可能几个小时就完成
There's no way to pull it together in a few hours.
有可能的
I believe there is.
在这个组织的支持下
With the support of this group.
支持谁
Support for whom?
支持那个我们都不咋了解的托尼吗
This Tony Almeida we barely know?
袭击后的计划呢
And what about postattack plans?
该组织怎样以我们想要的方式完成使命
How's this group going to end up where we need to be?
我同意  袭击事件发生之后
I agree. How we handle ourselves politically
我们怎样在政坛上求得自保
In the aftermath of this event
这点和计划袭击一样重要
Is just as important as the attack itself.
你的意见总是认为
It always has been in your opinion
在当前方案下  有没有充足时间
Is there Time then to achieve
来达到我们所有的目的
All our objectives in the current scenario?
这些问题有些仍悬而未决
Not with the same level of certainty.
其保密的程度也大相径庭
Or anonymity.
没错
That's right.
结果很肯定的
Well,then,maybe it's,uh,definitive.
什么意思
What do you mean?
等待时机并无消极影响
There's no downside to waiting.
但是鲁莽的行为常常是失败的原因
There's a huge downside to going in unprepared.
一旦出了岔子
Things go wrong,
我们都会暴露
We're looking at exposure for all of us
不  我不是这么认为
No,no,I still don't see it that way.
先生们
Gentlemen.
女士们
Ladies.
我在你们的争论中
I've listened to your comments
听到了好主意
And there's wisdom in what I've heard.
但是还有一点你们没有想到
But there's also wisdom in something I haven't heard.
乔纳斯·霍奇斯是一个我型我素的人
Jonas Hodges was a loose cannon,
现在已经成功地摆脱了他
And the group is well rid of him.
但是他疯狂的行为对我们来说  倒不无益处
But,in his lunacy,he did us a favor.
一半工作他都做好了
He did half our job for us.
远不止一半
More than half.
他把这个国家推向了危机边缘
He pushed this country to the brink.
没有比这更好的了
You don't get many gifts like that.
我们要抓住这次机会
I say we take it.
现在马上进行投票表决
We have a quorum,I'd like to call for an immediate vote.
托尼
Tony.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
你自己看吧
Take a look.
我们可以放手干了
We're a go.
-霍奇斯现在何处  -走廊尽头
- Where's Hodges now? - Down the hall.
我们设了一个安全的医疗套间
We've set up a medical suite in secure.
死亡证明呢
And the death certificate?
已经好了
Done.
外界只会知道
As far as the world knows,he's molding on a slab
-他已经被验尸官盖上白布了  -保持这样
- At the coroner's. - Keep it that way.
除非必须不要让任何人知道他还活着
No one knows he's alive unless they have to.
只有救护车驾驶员
No,just the ambulance driver,
医疗队和三个警卫知道
The medical team and three security.
都是信得过的人
All trustworthy.
等会
Wait.
你确定他能胜任这事么
Are you sure he's up for this?
我知道发生了什么事
I know what happened out there.
药物起作用了  他没事的
Medication worked. He'll be okay.
我不是说痉挛的问题
I'm not talking about the seizure.
我是说托尼·阿尔梅达的境遇对他的影响
I'm talking about the Tony Almeida situation.
怎么了
What about it?
他的前搭档背叛了他
His former partner betrays him,
想杀了你们所有人
He tries to have you all killed...
杰克肯定会感觉很不好
Jack must have some feelings about that.
是啊
Yeah.
我想这也是激励他继续下去的原因
Yeah,I think it's what's keeping him going.
听我说
Listen to me.
有人在吗
Is anyone listening?
知道你们在监视
I know you're watching.
我看到了摄像头
I see the cameras!
我知道你们在监视
I know you're watching.
你知道你们干了些什么吗
Do you realize what you people have done?
这不是救了我
You didn't save me,
你们害了我家人
You killed my family!
你们害了他们
You killed them!
害了他们
Killed them.
-他清醒多久了  -10分钟
- How long has he been conscious? - Ten minutes.
从醒了就一直在说他的家人
He's been talking about his family ever since.
布置了生物监控仪器
Biometrics are over here.
心脏呼吸及红外体温监测  一切尽在掌握
Cardiac,respiratory,plus dermal infrared.
很好  那样我们就能判断他是不是在撒谎了
Good. We'll know if he's lying.
杰克
Jack,
总统也在看着呢
The president is monitoring this.
中士  求你了
Sergeant,I'm asking you,
两个军人之间的协议  把你的枪给我
Soldier to soldier,let me have your firearm.
我只会用一颗子弹
I'll use one... one bullet on myself.
求你了
Please.
放松点  霍奇斯先生
Relax,Mr. Hodges.
你已经死了
You're already dead.
中士
Sergeant.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是杰克·鲍尔
My name is Jack Bauer.
现在我是你家人
And right now,I'm the only chance
能继续活下去的唯一希望
Your wife and children have to stay alive.
说清楚
Explain that to me.
想杀你灭口的人不知道你还活着
The people that wanted you dead don't know you survived.
告诉我们他们的名字
Tell us who they are,
我们就会帮助你继续假死
And we'll keep it that way.
如果你提供给我们有价值的线索
The president has agreed to provide you with a death
总统会提供死亡证明
Certificate and witness protection in exchange
和证人保护计划给你
For actionable information.
我看不下去了
I can't watch this anymore.
你要是拒绝
If you refuse,it'll be released
我们会告诉媒体你还活着
To the press that you are alive and in our custody
并在我们的监管中很好的配合
And that you're cooperating.
剩下的就交给你那帮朋友了
We'll let your friends take care of the rest.
我家人是无辜的
My family is innocent.
总统不会怎么做的
The president would never allow that to happen.
她不会忍心的
She doesn't have the stomach for it.
你可能说的没错
You might be right about that.
但是别搞错了
But make no mistake about it,sir.
我会
I do.
相信我
Trust me.
为了你的家人
Do your family a favor.
告诉我你的同伙的名字
Just tell me who you've been working with.
我是
I am...
以前
I was...
是一个有共同理想的组织的一员
Part of a larger group of like minds.
你说像斯塔克伍德一样的公司
You mean,other companies like Starkwood.
我是说比政府更能
I mean people who can protect this country
保护这个国家的人
Better than any government ever could.
全国起码有数百家私营军事企业
There are hundreds of private military companies
那可是成千上万的人
In this country,we're talking tens of thousands of people.
可只有少数
But only a handful
有远见卓识  知道该做什么
With the guts and the vision to do what was necessary.
做什么
And what is that?
我们计划在明年早些时候
The plan was to launch simultaneous attacks
对多个大城市
Early next year.
发动同步攻击
Multiple cities.
公众就会意识到
So the public would finally see
政府无法保全他们
That the government can't protect them.
然后他们会要求强力举措  我们就借此介入
They'd demand drastic measures and we'd step in.
你怎么向美国民众解释
How would you justify that to the American people?
很简单
Simple.
嫁祸他人
Offload the blame.
我们会支持那些
We were going to supply the enemies
想摧毁这个国家的敌人
That want to destroy this country.
张三李四王二麻子
Muhammed this,achmed that.
那些根本不存在的虚构组织
From sleeper cells the apologists say don't even exist.
这个你应该最清楚
You of all people should understand.
清楚什么
Understand what?
我昨天的听证会我看了
I watched the senate hearing yesterday,
很为你打抱不平  他们不应该这样对你
And I was disgusted with how you were treated.
你应该被视为英雄
You should be regarded as a hero,
而不是罪犯
Not a criminal.
我犯了法
I broke the law.
你只是本能地
You were following
去保护你的国家  就像我
Your instinct to protect your country,just like me.
霍奇斯先生  我需要你说出
Mr. Hodges,I need the names
同党的名字
Of the people that you are working with.
我一生都致力于保护这个国家
I have spent my entire life protecting this country
免受外敌的侵扰
From enemies large and small.
我白手起家创立了斯塔克伍德
I created Starkwood from the ground up.
并为政府立下了汗马功劳
And the government used us to great effect.
现在他们却要过河拆桥
And now they think they can just throw us away.
你是要告诉我  你做这些
Are you telling me that this has been
只是想保护你的合同  你的利益吗
About protecting your contracts,about money?
我试图告诉那些政客美国有多么脆弱
I tried to tell the politicians how vulnerable we are,
可他们根本不在意
And they wouldn't listen.
所以我们决定展示给他们看
So we decided to show them.
用生化武器攻击你自己的国家吗
By attacking your own country with a biological weapon?
杀害无辜的百姓吗
By killing innocent people?
没错  牺牲一小部分人
Yes,a few innocent lives would be lost,
是为了拯救更多的人
But only to save the greater number.
有勇气作出这些艰难的决定
Having the courage to make those hard choices
在这点上  我们还是有很多相同之处
Gives us a lot in common,Mr. Bauer.
我来解释给你听吧
Let me explain something to you.
我和你毫无相同之处可言
You and I have absolutely nothing in common.
你今天的所作所为是想要
All that you have done today is create a scenario
攻击你自己的国家
By attacking your own country
来展示你的价值
That has made you valuable again.
这完全是一次
Today has been nothing short
歇斯底里的权力之争
Of a desperate grab for power,
而且失败了
And it has failed.
你输了  除非你想我去公开
You have failed,and unless you want me to go public
你还活着这个事实
With the fact that you are still alive,
快把你同伙的名字告诉我
You are gonna give me the names of the people that you've been working with.
-我  我没有  -我要名单
- I-I don't have them. - I want the names.
-我不知道  -名单
- I don't have any. - I want the names!
我真不知道
I don't know any!
好吧
Fine.
帮我接通华盛顿邮报的艾米
Patch me through to Amy at the washington post.
不要
No.
艾米  我是杰克  我需要发布一项声明
Amy,it's Jack. I have a statement I need to make.
等一下
Wait!
-等等  等下  -告诉我名字
- Wait! wait! wait! wait! - Give me the names!
我发誓  我发誓我不知道
I swear... I swear I don't have them.
整个计划都是匿名的
This whole project was... was based on anonymity.
我们从不亲自见面
We never met in person.
由中间人来处理一切事务  一个女人
Everything was handled through an intermediary,a woman.
她从未透露过身份
She never told me who she was.
从没说过她的名字
She never told me her name.
我也没有问
I never asked her.
和给你毒药的是同一人吗
The same woman that gave you the poison?
是的
Yes,yes.
艾米  不好意思  情况有变
Amy,I'm sorry. something's come up.
我晚点打给你
I've got to call you back.
随便你自己怎么说
You tell yourself whatever you want.
你是个卖国贼
You are a traitor.
你承诺过给我证人保护的
Witness protection was your promise.
是的
Yeah.
总统阁下  你听到了
Madam President,did you hear everything
霍奇斯的话吗
That Hodges had to say?
是的  他说的可信吗
Yes. Is any of it even credible?
很可信  生物监测器表明
All of it is. Biometric monitors here indicate
他没有撒谎
That he was telling the truth.
不管他们是谁  这个组织
Whoever they are,this group just went
为了拿到这个毒气罐
Through an awful lot of trouble
费了一番波折
To get their hands on that last canister.
很明显他们的计划仍在进行
It seems very clear to me that their plan is still on.
-你是说另一次攻击  -是的  阁下
- You mean another attack? - Yes,ma'am.
我认为您要假定他们会发动袭击
I think you should proceed under the assumption
并做好部署准备
That they might strike immediately.
等一下
Hold on.
霍奇斯说明年开始
Hodges said some Time next year.
不  霍奇斯说那是以往的计划
No. Hodges said that was the plan.
照他这次制造的混乱来看
Given the chaos that he created today,
最明智的战略手段是马上行动
The smart strategic move would be to act right now.
现在  我觉得毒气罐仍旧在这个区域
Now,I believe the canister is still in this area,
我们得向国土安全局示警
So we're gonna have to alert Homeland,
让他们马上核实目标并进行搜捕
Have them start identifying and raiding targets.
霍奇斯说计划是要
Hodges said that the plan was
涉及到一些有恐怖主义倾向的组织
To enlist parties with terrorist ties.
这样看来  那会是我们的切入点
At this point,I think that might be our most solid lead.
总统阁下  我同意沃克探员说的
Madam President,I agree with agent Walker.
我们需要拟一份当前威胁评估
We need to make an immediate threat assessment
其中囊括所有已知的恐怖活动
With focus on all known terrorist activity.
我们获取消息的最快途径
The fastest way for us to get that information
是接入反恐组的服务器
Is to gain access to the CTU servers
迈尔参议员调查之后
That have been sealed as a result
那服务器就被封掉了
Of senator Mayer's investigation.
我马上下令重新启用
I'll have them recommissioned immediately.
以后政府的内部资源
And consider the resources of this government
就归你自行支配了  杰克
At your disposal,Jack.
谢谢  总统阁下
Thank you,ma'am.
快准备好那些服务器
I need those servers right away.
他们在三楼的证据储物柜里
They're in doj evidence lockers on the third floor.
我让科技部的人去弄
I'll have I.T. break them out.
很好
Okay,good.
我们组新换了一班分析员
We have a new shift of analysts coming in,
你可以告诉他们你要找的
If you can tell them what you're looking for.
不行  没时间了
No,we don't have Time.
现在需要的是熟悉协议的人
We need someone who already knows the protocols.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
给我那些服务器就行了
Just get me those servers.
谁
Who is it?
是我  杰克
Hey,it's me Jack.
杰克  你去哪了
Jack,where the hell are you?
联邦调查局总部
The FBI headquarters.
我一整晚都在试图联系你
I've been trying to reach you all night.
没人告诉我发生什么了
No one will tell me anything.
比尔真的出事了吗
Is it true about Bill?
是的
Yeah,I'm afraid so.
发生什么了
What happened?
他在围攻白宫时牺牲了
He was killed during the White House siege.
克罗伊  你要知道
Chloe,you should know,
比尔牺牲自己救了总统
Bill sacrificed his life to save the president.
听我说  威胁还没结束
Listen to me. This threat is not over.
我们觉得在这附近会有一次生化武器袭击
We believe that there's going to be a biological attack somewhere in the area.
很快  我需要你帮忙来阻止这次袭击
Soon. I need your help to stop it.
怎样做
How?
重组反恐小组的服务器
I need you to reconstitute the CTU servers.
反恐组解散后就被撤销了
They were seized when the CTU was decommissioned.
我没有权限查看
I don't have access to them.
你到这就会有了
You will by the Time you get here.
谁在做
Who's doing this?
我们没让全员参与
We don't have all the players.
等你赶到这  我再告诉你详情
I'll fill you in with as much as I know when you get here.
我派了车去旅馆接你
I'm sending a car over to your hotel.
派车过来吧
Send a car.
莫里斯  快醒醒
Morris,wake up.
什么  你怎么又跟我说话了
What? Are you speaking to me again now?
我要走了
I have to go.
你带普雷斯科特离开这个城市
I need you to take Prescott and get out of the city.
-为什么  -我刚和杰克通过电话
- Why? - I just spoke with Jack.
即将会有另一次袭击
There's going to be another attack.
这次是生化武器
This Time,it's biological.
既然这样  我们一起离开
Okay,then we'll all get out of here together.
我不能  调查局还需要我
I can't. FBI needs me.
可上一次你为那些人工作
But the last Time you worked for these people,
他们逮捕了你
They arrested you.
我知道
I know.
可只有我才能让服务器重新上线
But I'm the only one that can get the servers back online.
我不会把你留在这里的
Well,I'm not gonna leave you here.
尤其这里还有被生化武器袭击的可能
Not with the possibility of a biological attack.
拜托了
Please.
我是唯一一个能办到这件事的人
I'm the only one that can do this.
杰克需要我
And Jack needs me.
我只想要你和雷斯科特都安全
And I just need for you and Prescott to be safe.
好吗
Okay?
回头家里见
I'll see you back at home.
你要多加小心
Just... be careful.
我会的
I will.
好了  我们开始前  每个人确保
All right,before we begin,everyone make sure
自己都获得了最新分组数据简报
You have your updated briefing packets,
以及疾控中心的调查摘要
And the latest CDC abstract.
-杰克  可以开始了  -谢谢
- Jack,whenever you're ready. - Thank you.
我知道今天你们很多人都失去了朋友同事
I know many of you have lost friends and colleagues today.
我也是
I have,too.
很不幸  现在不是哀悼
Unfortunately,the Time to mourn these brave men and women
这些勇士们的时候
Is going to have to wait.
因为你们都知道
'cause,as many of you are already aware,
我们的东海岸某处
We are facing the threat of a terrorist event
面临着恐怖袭击的威胁
Somewhere on the eastern seaboard.
我们并没有准确的情报
We don't have specific intel
告知这次袭击的时间
As to the Time table of this attack,
但是我们有理由相信
But we do have reason to believe that
袭击的幕后主使会计划立即发动袭击
The people that are behind this will want to strike immediately?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我是蒂姆·莫兰  外勤探员
Tim Moran,field ops.
幕后主使是谁
Who are the people behind this?
目前为止  我们只有2名嫌疑人
Right now,we only have two confirmed suspects.
托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony Almeida
还有和他合作的那个女人
And the woman he's been working with.
我们还在核实她的身份
We're still trying to identify her.
我们假定  他俩是更大阴谋的一部分
The assumption is,the two of them are part of a broader
这些请参见各位手中的简报资料
Conspiracy as outlined in your briefing material.
是什么性质的袭击呢
And the nature of the attack?
资料上说是生化武器
All it says here is biological.
病原体实际上是一种朊病毒的变体
The actual pathogen is a prion variant,designed to attack
用来摧毁中枢神经系统
The central nervous system and ulTimately destroy it.
我们知道目标吗
Do we know what the target is?
不  我们还不清楚运载装置的具体细节
No,not yet. We're also unclear on the specifics of the delivery device.
那我们目前知道什么
Well,what leads do we have?
现在
Right now,
我们只能凭经验判断
We are solely working off an operational theory
那些幕后主使们
That the people that are behind this
需要伪造证据
Will need to manufacture evidence
来把这次袭击嫁祸到
In an effort to offload the blame for this attack
其它有恐怖主义倾向的
To either another group or an individual
组织或是个人身上
With terrorist sympathies.
以此来造成公众恐慌
During the ensuing panic,
这些人就能以维持时局稳定
These people will move in and seize power
为借口介入  进而夺取政权
Under the guise of creating and maintaining stability.
所以  我们现在的任务就是
So,our job here is to look for traces
寻找伪造证据的蛛丝马迹
Of that manufactured evidence.
怎么找
How exactly?
搜索那些可疑的财政交易
Pattern searches of suspicious financial transactions.
窃听器的密码截取
Keyword intercepts of existing wiretaps,
包括网站和电子邮件
Websites and e-mails.
以及过去6个月里
And data-mining all
国家安全局和中央情报局
NSA and CIA intelligence
所截获的有关伊斯兰圣战主义活动的情报
On jihadist activities over the past six months.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
如此大规模的监控不仅违法
Not only is that type of blanket surveillance illegal.
我们也没有能力办到
We don't have the capacity to pull it off.
这样的搜索方式
The search algorithms
-并不存在  -不  是有的
- Simply don't exist.- yes,they do.
-在反恐组  -那些服务器已被撤销了
- At CTU. - Those servers were decommissioned.
现在不再这样了  它们在这
Not anymore. They're here.
我们马上可以安装恢复
We're in the process of installing them now.
那我们算什么  反恐小组精简版吗
Well,what does that make us,CTU-lite?
据我所知
Last I heard,
调查局是受联邦法令约束的政府部门
The bureau was a federal entity bound by federal statute.
詹尼斯  照做  要不我找其他愿做的来
Janis, do this or I will find someone else who will.
我没时间跟你争论
I do not have Time to argue.
我不是在争论  我只是在问
I'm not arguing. I'm asking.
继续
Moving on.
由我来接待她就行了  谢谢
I've got her from here. Thanks.
杰克
Jack. Hey.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
你脸色好差
You look like hell.
-你没事吧  -我没事
- Are you all right? - I'm fine.
你看起来可不是这样
You don't look fine.
也许有点累
Maybe a little tired.
收到我发给你的报告了吗
Did you get the report I sent you?
收到了  我在过来的路上看过了
Yeah. I read it on the way over.
-太可怕了  可信度高吗  -很高
- It's terrifying. How real is this? - Real.
我们能访问反恐组的服务器了  对吧
We're getting access to the CTU servers, right?
没错  已经连线了
Yeah. They're coming online now.
我不是应该对这进行监控吗
Shouldn't I be supervising this?
是的  听着
Yeah. Look,
在我们开始前  我得跟你说点事
There's something I need to talk to you about before we get started.
这真让我难以启齿
There's no easy way for me to say this.
托尼要对这些袭击事件负责
But Tony's been responsible for these attacks.
那不可能
That's not possible.
他一直在利用你跟比尔
He was using you and Bill all along.
他一直在为一些私人军工企业做事
He's really been working for a group of private military firms
企图破坏国家稳定  夺取政权
Trying to destabilize this country in an effort to seize power.
到目前为止
So far today,
他今天的行为已经造成上百人丧生
His actions have cost the lives of hundreds of people.
还威胁着更多人的生命
But he's threatening thousands more.
这真没道理啊
It doesn't make any sense.
我知道他因为米歇尔的死痛不欲生  但
I know he was devastated over michelle, but...
克罗伊  他不是你的朋友
Chloe, he's not your friend.
你认识的那个托尼  已经不存在了
The Tony that you knew... he doesn't exist anymore.
他一定有什么苦衷
There has to be a reason.
什么苦衷
A reason for what?
让两辆客机坠毁
Bringing down two passenger planes?
偷袭25名联邦探员
Trying to ambush 25 federal agents?
克罗伊  他想杀了我
Chloe, he tried to kill me.
他背叛了我们所有人  你  我
He betrayed us all... you, me,
还有比尔
And Bill,
现在我们唯一的责任
And right now our only responsibility
就是要阻止他
Is to stop him.
我需要知道你能够把他当做敌人
Now, I need to know that you can treat him
你能跟我一起来阻止他
As an enemy combatant, that you are with me on this.
好吧  你说做什么我就做
Okay, I'll do whatever you say.
不  我要知道你在这件事上跟我是一致的
No, I need to know that you are with me on this.
我跟你是一致的
I'm with you.
好吧
Okay.
走吧
Let's go.
他叫吉布安·阿尔扎利安
His name is jibraan al-zarian.
27岁
27 years old.
他是卡布罗拉花岗岩建筑厂的散工
He's a day laborer at cabrera granite construction.
移民情况呢
Immigration status?
非法
Illegal.
他的签证一月就到期了
His visa expired as of january.
跟极端主义团体有联系吗
Ties to any extremist groups?
没有任何联系  但他心里一定有怨愤
No, none, but there's definitely anger there.
在巴基斯坦边境一次美军空袭中父母双亡
Both parents were killed in a U.S. Air strike by the PakistanI border.
他当时只有11岁
He was 11 at the Time.
符合犯罪心理特征
Fits the psych profile.
有点自闭  不为同事所熟悉
Bit of a loner, a mystery to his coworkers,
我们编造了剩下的行为模式
And we build the rest.
家人呢
What about the family?
有一个弟弟  差不多是他独自抚养的
One younger brother, who he's pretty much raised on his own.
很完美  对吧
It's perfect, huh?
尽管还不知道今晚首府人民能否睡个好觉
Though it is doubtful that anyone sleeps very well in D.C. tonight,
经历了今天一轮恐怖袭击后
A certain calm was set over the streets.
全国人民都很害怕
After an unprecedented series of terror attacks
但人民的情绪已经稍稍缓和了
Left people all over the country shaken and demavery hungry.
在泰勒总统讲话里
In her speech, president Taylor went a long way...
早上好
Morning.
倒点橘子水喝吧
Pour yourself some orange juice.
我不是很饿
I'm not really very hungry.
坐下  吃一次早饭吧
Sit down,eat some breakfast for once.
不吃不利于身体健康
It's unhealthy not to.
你起来干嘛
What are you doing up anyway?
我
I,uh,
睡不着
Couldn't sleep.
听着  今天一下班
Listen,uh,I want you to come
就赶紧回家
home straight after the work today?
好吗
Okay?
不要耽搁
No delaying.
为什么
Why?
以防万一
Just in case.
防什么
In case of what?
袭击啊  恐怖分子啊
These attacks,this terrorism...
新闻里全是这些
It's all over the news.
我们穆斯林今天没好日子过
Okay,it's not a good day to be a muslim.
吉布安  穆斯林和这些无关
Jibraan,muslims had nothing to do with it.
这点无关紧要
Doesn't matter.
相信我  没人在乎这个
Nobody cares,believe me.
很多同事还以为我是波多黎各人
Most of the guys at my work think I'm puerto rican anyway.
到时间了
It's about Time.
请进
Come in.
打扰一下  泰勒小姐
Excuse me,Ms. Taylor.
什么事
What is it?
司法部长让我提醒你
The attorney general asked me to check in with you.
他在等着签署你
He is waiting to sign off on a document
正在看的文件
I was told you were reviewing.
有人跟你说过
Anyone happen to mention to you
这文件内容吗
What this document is about?
没有
No,ma'am.
我觉得他们也不会
No,I imagine they wouldn't.
这是高度机密
It's a secret,Highly classified.
我可不在乎
Not that I give a damn.
这是让乔纳斯·霍奇斯可以
It's a get-out- of-jail-free card
大摇大摆走出监狱的绿色通道
For Jonas Hodges,
那个杀了我弟弟
The bastard responsible for my brother's death
和许多平民的混蛋
And so many others.
我不明白
I don't understand.
霍奇斯先生死在医院里了
Mr. Hodges died in the hospital.
真是这样就好了  但事实是他没死
I wish that were the case,but no,
一旦司法部长签署了证人保护文件
And once the A.G. Signs this witness protection agreement,
霍奇斯就会舒舒服服地
Hodges is going to live out his days
在隐姓埋名中继续过他的日子去了
in comfort and anonymity
而我弟弟却躺在阿林顿墓地死不瞑目
While my brother lies in his grave in Arlington Cemetery.
亚伦  你说这公平吗
Does that sound like justice to you,Aaron?
不  女士  不公平
No,ma'am,it does not.
但我妈却认同
And yet my mother saw fit
以奖励这个混蛋来换取他的合作的做法
To reward this monster for his cooperation.
我认为那对总统来说
Well,I'm sure it was a difficult decision
也是个艰难的决定
For the president to make.
没有你想象中的难
Not difficult enough.
我妈也许可以忍受  但我不能
My mother may be able to live with it, but I'm not sure I can.
泰勒女士  这种情况的豁免
Ms. Taylor,I have seen the guilty
不是一次两次了
walk free many Times.
我理解你的愤怒和挫败感
I understand your anger and frustration,
我也真的很难过
And I am genuinely sorry.
告诉司法部长文件我看过了
Tell the A.G. I've reviewed the agreement
可以继续
And we can move ahead.
谢谢
Thank you,ma'am.
有什么我可以为你做的吗
Is there anything else that I can do for you?
除了把乔纳斯·霍奇斯杀了  没有了
Other than kill Jonas Hodges,no.
对不起  亚伦
I'm sorry,Aaron.
我不是这个意思
I didn't mean that.
只是发泄一下
I was just venting.
女士  失陪
Ma'am.
你好
Hello?
马丁
Martin?
我是奥利维亚·泰勒
It's Olivia Taylor.
吵醒你了吗
Did I wake you?
我想是的
Well,as a matter of fact,yes.
几点了
What Time is it?
快四点了
Almost 4:00.
我还以为你不会在家呢
Actually I didn't expect to catch you at home.
还以为你在佛罗里达
I thought you were in Florida
反对加纳的竞选
Doing opposition for the Gainor campaign.
没有  好像不是很管用
No,that didn't really work out.
为什么
Why not?
只是从政界高官的偏好来看
Let's just say that my methods were a little hardball
我的手段有点太强硬了
For the governor's taste.
我能帮你什么  奥利维亚
So... what can I do for you,Olivia?
听说白宫遇袭了吗
You heard about the attack on the White House?
对  看到你妈妈的全国演说
Yeah,I watched your mother's address to the nation.
印象深刻啊
Really impressive.
她总是惊喜连连  对吧
She continues to surprise,doesn't she?
马丁  我需要你帮忙
Listen,martin,I need your help.
见个面可以吗
Can we meet?
-现在  -是啊
- Now? - Yeah.
什么事  奥利维亚
Well,what's this about,Olivia?
电话上不方便讲
I can't talk about it over the phone.
这三更半夜的
Well,it's the middle of the night,you know?
你总要说清楚点
Y-you got to do better than that.
在亚特兰大时  咱选了海沃斯做竞选伙伴
We were in a dive hotel bar in Atlanta Right after we picked Hayworth
随后咱去了酒店的潜水酒吧
To be the running mate on the ticket.
他滥用处方药的事情
There was an issue regarding his abuse of a certain prescription drug
当地媒体执意抓着不放
And a local reporter who couldn't be persuaded to shut up about it.
我记得你找到我说
I remember you turned to me and said
没有什么问题
There was no problem
是不能解决或消灭的
That couldn't be handled or eliminated.
我当时醉了
Well,I was drunk.
你是认真的
You were serious.
好吧
You know,you're right.
我们是不能在电话里讨论这个
We shouldn't be talking about this over the phone.
你什么时候能到白宫
How soon can you be at the White House?
15分钟怎么样
How's 15 minutes sound?
很好
Good.
好了吗
You done with that yet?
我对这些指令不是很了解
I'm not familiar with these commands.
不要用2号服务器启动子网络
Oh,you don't want to boot the subnet with server two.
那有一个错误还没来及修正
It has a faulty bus that we weren't able to fix
就被你们扣押了
Before you guys impounded it.
要不你来接手吧
Well,maybe you'd like to take over.
只要能让它正常运转就好
Only if you want it to work right.
我也不喜欢这个
I don't like this either.
-有问题吗  -没错
- Is there a problem? - Yes,there is.
我真不想干这个
I'm not comfortable doing this.
我同意了  但并不喜欢
I agreed to it,but I don't like it.
你不喜欢什么啊
What exactly aren't you comfortable with?
首先这违反了人权法案
Uh,well,the Bill of Rights being violated,for one,
所以  如果你要做一些
So if you're going to be doing anything
严重违法的事情  请你
Grossly illegal,please...
我们会通知你
We'll make sure we notify you
让你离开这的
So you can leave the building.
哎哟  大独裁家嘛
Hello,big brother.
听着  如果你觉得你的抱怨
Look,if you think your need
比那些依靠我们保护的生命
To complain is more important than the lives of the people
更重要的话  到别处抱怨去吧你
That are counting on us,go whine somewhere else!
-杰克  没关系的  -不 很有关系
- Jack, it's okey. - No, it's not okey.
大卫·帕默总统重新启用这些服务器
President David Palmer recommissioned these servers
是因为他认为这对国家安全很重要
Because he felt it was vital to national security!
帕默总统已经做了决定
President Palmer made the call!
你觉得够了吗
Is that going to be good enough for you?!
回答我
Answer me!
是的
Yes.
他出什么问题了
There's something really wrong with him.
他说帕默总统
He said president Palmer.
其实他的意思是泰勒
He meant Taylor.
还说了两次
He said it twice.
又怎么了
What is this now?
可能保险丝出问题了
Probably a fuse.
你尽量多吃点
Here,you do what you can to finish up.
我去看看电表箱
I'm gonna go check the box.
吉布安
Jibraan!
哈米德
Hamid?
吉布
Jibra...
哈米德
Hamid?
闭嘴就没事
Keep your mouth shut and no one gets hurt.
-你是谁  你要干什么  -闭嘴
- Who are you? What do you want? - Shut up!
你把我弟弟怎么样了
What did you do to my brother?
-哈米德  -再多说一句
- Hamid! - One more word,
我就一枪毙了你
I put a bullet in your brain.
明白了
Understand?
-明白了吗  -是的
- You understand?! - Yes!